http://www.rothstaffing.com/policies/#termsofservice

Effective January 21, 2020
Roth Staffing Companies, L.P. and its divisions, affiliates and subsidiaries (collectively, “Roth Staffing” or “Company”), is committed to protecting the privacy of every individual who utilizes its websites (the “Sites”) and does business with the Company. This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the information you provide to us in using our Sites and the services provided through our Sites and the mobile applications we offer (collectively referred to as the “Services”). Please take a minute to review this Privacy Policy and contact the Company with any concerns or questions at the address below.
We may change this Privacy Policy at our discretion and at any time. If we do, we will post an amended version on this webpage. Please review this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Sites and Services after any such amendment signifies your acceptance thereof.
Personally Identifiable Information the Company Collects Online
As a staffing services provider presenting individuals to potential employers, Roth Staffing collects personally identifiable information from you when you interact with our Sites or Services. “Personally Identifiable Information” is individually identifiable information about an individual consumer that we collect online and that we maintain in an accessible form. We collect the following types of Personally Identifiable Information:
Information You Provide
We may collect the following Personally Identifiable Information that you voluntarily provide to us:
Create a Profile. If you create an account with Ultimate® Staffing Services, Ledgent®, Ledgent Finance and Accounting®, Ledgent Technology®, Adams & Martin Group®, or About Talent®, we will collect your name, address, phone number, and e-mail address. We also will collect other information such as your resume, username, password, security question/answer, and previous employment information.
Apply for a Job. If you apply for a position (and do not already have an account), we will collect your name and e-mail address. We also will collect other information such as your resume, zip code, job application information, and password.
Sign up for Job Alerts. If you use our “Sign up for Job Alerts” feature, we will collect your e-mail address.
Employee.  If your application is accepted and we hire you to work for one of our clients, we will collect additional information such as your social security number and other employment-related information.
Refer a Friend to Us. If you use our “Refer a Friend to Us” feature, we will collect your name, e-mail address and phone number, and the name, e-mail address, city/location, and phone number of the person you refer to us.
Refer a Job to a Friend. If you use our “Refer a Job to a Friend” feature, we will collect your name and e-mail address and the recipient’s name and e-mail address. You also have the option of sending us a message, which may result in you providing additional Personally Identifiable Information.
Customer. If you are a customer and place a job order or submit contract information online, we will collect names, addresses, phone numbers, and e-mail addresses. We also will collect other information such as titles and company names.
VideoSelect. If you use our “VideoSelect” feature or mobile application, we will collect your name and e-mail address. We also will collect other information such as a username, password and video of you answering questions.
Publications. If you download one of our publications, such as our Salary Guides, we will collect your name, address, e-mail address, and phone number. You also may submit other information such as your job title.
Webinars. If you register for a webinar, we will collect your name and e-mail address.
Remarkable Experiences. If you send us a story for inclusion in our “Remarkable Experiences” feature, we will collect your e-mail address and any other Personally Identifiable Information you provide in your story.
Roth Heroes. If you nominate a hero through our “Roth Heroes” feature, we will collect your name, e-mail address, and any other Personally Identifiable Information you provide in your nomination explanation.
Blog. If you subscribe to one of our blogs, we will collect your e-mail address.
Work with Us. If you contact us to be a client, supplier or channel partner, we will collect your name, e-mail address, and phone number. We also will collect other information such as your company name and specialty.
Support. If you contact us for support, we will collect your name, e-mail address and phone number. We also will collect other information such as your company name and description of the issue.
Careers. If you apply to work directly for us, we will collect your name, e-mail address, and phone number. We also will collect other information such as your resume, state/city, work experience, and education.
Contact Us. If you use our “Contact Us” feature, we will collect your name, e-mail address, and phone number. You also have the option of sending us a message, which may result in you providing Personally Identifiable Information.
Information as You Navigate Our Site
We automatically collect certain Personally Identifiable Information through your use of our Sites and Services, such as the following:
Usage Information. We collect information such as which of the pages on the Sites you access, the frequency of access, and what you click on while on the Sites.
Device Information. We collect information about the device you are using, such as hardware model, operating system, application version number, and browser.
Mobile Device Information. In addition to the Device Information listed above, when you access our Sites via a browser on your mobile device, we collect and aggregate information about whether you are accessing the Sites via a mobile device or tablet, device type, and carrier.
Location Information. We collect location information from visitors to our Sites on a city-regional basis.
User Flow. We collect information on the sites from which you navigate to our Sites and where you navigate away to.
Third Party Information
In some cases, we may receive certain Personally Identifiable Information from you about a third party. For example, if you nominate someone to be a Roth Hero, you will be asked to provide Personally Identifiable Information about that person. If you submit any Personally Identifiable Information about another individual to us, you are responsible for making sure that you have the authority to do so and to allow us to use their Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Other Information
We collect Personally Identifiable Information from other sources such as social media providers. This information includes names, e-mail addresses, phone numbers, employment history and resumes.
How the Company Uses Personally Identifiable Information
We collect Personally Identifiable Information to develop a thorough understanding of the individual’s work experience, skills and abilities and of the customer’s job requirements. Roth Staffing uses this Personally Identifiable Information to enhance its services, fulfill customers’ and candidates’ requests for job placement, personalize their experience and provide them with special offers they may find valuable. Roth Staffing will contact previous employers to verify information provided regarding prior work history but will not knowingly contact current employers without express written permission to do so.
We also will use your Personally Identifiable Information to process your account registration, communicate with you regarding our products and services that we feel may be of interest to you, provide support, maintain and improve our Sites and Services, defend our legal rights and the rights of others, efficiently maintain our business, and comply with applicable law.
How the Company Shares Personally Identifiable Information
In order to assist individuals in their job search and customers in their job placements, to facilitate our efficient use of your information, to provide you with content and/or resources, to fulfill a request you make of us, or to otherwise provide our services, Personally Identifiable Information is shared with the following third parties:
Service providers and suppliers. We may share Personally Identifiable Information with our third-party service providers and suppliers who perform business functions and services on our behalf and to perform administrative and operational work in support of Roth Staffing’s relationship with you. The service providers are subject to contractual and other legal obligations to preserve the confidentiality of your Personally Identifiable Information and to use the data they need to perform their services or functions.
Customers and prospective customers. Customers and prospective customers may request professional and employment-related information for purposes of evaluating an individual’s credentials, skills and experience. Customers may also need to approve and process timesheet information or perform other administrative functions to effectuate our payment of temporary employees.
Candidates for temporary employment or direct placement. We may share Personally Identifiable Information of our customers or prospective customers to candidates such as when a candidate must know information about whom to contact when going on an interview or an assignment with a customer or prospective customer.
As required or appropriate by law. We may disclose Personally Identifiable Information to regulatory authorities, government authorities or courts to comply with applicable laws, the service of legal process, or if we reasonably believe that such action is necessary to (a) comply with the law requiring such disclosure; (b) protect the rights or property of Roth Staffing or its affiliated companies; (c) prevent a crime or protect national security; or (d) protect the personal safety of the users or the public.
Business transfers or reorganizations. We also may disclose or transfer information to a third party in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings).
Subsidiaries. To the extent we have any wholly owned or majority-owned subsidiaries, we may share your Personally Identifiable Information to facilitate our services.
Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
We use cookies and other tracking technologies (such as pixels and web beacons) (collectively, “Cookies”), including for our marketing efforts. “Cookies” are small files of information that a website – when visited by a user- asks your browser to store on your device (e.g., computer, smartphone or tablet) in order to remember information about you, such as your language preference or login information. Those cookies are set by us and called first-party cookies. We also use third-party cookies – which are cookies from a domain different than the domain of the website you are visiting – for our advertising and marketing efforts. More specifically, we use cookies and other tracking technologies for the following purposes:
Strictly Necessary Cookies
These cookies are necessary for the website to function and cannot be switched off in our systems. They are usually only set in response to actions made by you which amount to a request for services, such as setting your privacy preferences, logging in or filling in forms. You can set your browser to block or alert you about these cookies, but some parts of the site will not then work. These cookies do not store any Personally Identifiable Information.
Social Media Cookies
These cookies are set by a range of social media services that we have added to the site to enable you to share our content with your friends and networks. They are capable of tracking your browser across other sites and building up a profile of your interests. This may impact the content and messages you see on other websites you visit. If you do not allow these cookies you may not be able to use or see these sharing tools.
Targeting Cookies
These cookies may be set through our site by our advertising partners. They may be used by those companies to build a profile of your interests and show you relevant adverts on other sites.    They do not store Personally Identifiable Information, but are based on uniquely identifying your browser and internet device. If you do not allow these cookies, you will experience less targeted advertising.
Performance Cookies
These cookies allow us to count visits and traffic sources so we can measure and improve the performance of our site. They help us to know which pages are the most and least popular and see how visitors move around the site. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. If you do not allow these cookies, we will not know when you have visited our site, and will not be able to monitor its performance.
Functional Cookies
These cookies enable the website to provide enhanced functionality and personalization. They may be set by us or by third party providers whose services we have added to our pages. If you do not allow these cookies, then some or all of these services may not function properly.
Links to Other Web Sites
Our Sites may contain links and references to other sites. Roth Staffing encourages you to review the privacy statements of these other sites so that you can understand how your information is collected, used and shared. Roth Staffing assumes no responsibility for the privacy statements or the content on Web sites not maintained by Roth Staffing.
E-Mail Addresses
Roth Staffing is fully committed to only sending you e-mail that you have an interest in receiving. We do not share your e-mail address with other parties at any time for any purpose whatsoever. This includes renting, bartering, selling, leasing or otherwise making your e-mail address available to any other company or organization unless required by a court or law enforcement.
Occasionally, Roth Staffing utilizes e-mail to share valuable information with those candidates who have requested to be kept informed regarding career searches, employment opportunities and special benefits available to them. Candidates may choose to opt out of these distributions at any time.
In addition, Roth Staffing utilizes e-mail to share valuable information with customers who have requested to be kept informed of staffing issues, technological innovations and special offers available to them. Customers may choose to unsubscribe from such e-mail campaign communications at any time by (1) clicking on the “unsubscribe” link that appears in these messages, (2) inputting their relevant e-mail address and (3) clicking “submit” to complete the unsubscribe process.
Roth Staffing utilizes the services of reputable third-party companies for the transmission of e-mail messages. The Company shares recipient email addresses with the third-party companies.  The third-party companies share usage information about recipients of Roth Staffing’s e-mails and visitors to Company Sites for the purpose of targeting future campaigns and upgrading visitor information used in reporting statistics. For this purpose, Roth Staffing and its third-party e-mail transmission company use tracking (images, javascript, and link tracking) to note your interaction with Company e-mail messages and to record some of the pages you visit on Company Sites. This information allows Roth Staffing to provide information that is tailored to your needs and interests.
Text Messages Terms
By registering to receive communications via Short Message Service, which is text (“SMS”), or Multi-Media Service (“MMS”), or Rich Communication Services (“RCS”) (collectively, “SMS/MMS Service”), you agree as follows:
Authorization: You certify that you are authorized: (a) to enroll the designated mobile phone number which you provide in your application or other documentation in the SMS/MMS Service, and (b) to incur any mobile message or data charges that may be incurred by participating in the SMS/MMS Service.
Opting In to SMS/MMS Service: By opting in to the SMS/MMS Service, you consent to these terms and to receive text message communications from Roth Staffing as described herein. A text message will be delivered to the mobile number you provided confirming that you opted-in to receive text messages. You are responsible for managing the types of texts (whether SMS or MMS) you receive.
You expressly consent and agree to accept and receive communications via text message to your mobile device and to the cellular/mobile telephone number(s) that you provided to us. The information in any message may be subject to certain time lags and/or delays.
Frequency of Messages: The number and frequency of SMS/MMS messages sent to your device depends on several factors, including the length of your assignment, number of recently posted jobs matching your search criteria, jobs that you have applied to or your resume, and if you have asked for help or support via text messaging.
To Stop Messages: Reply STOP to any text message you receive, or contact the IT Privacy Department at the contact information listed below. You consent that following such a request to unsubscribe, you will receive one (1) final message confirming that you have been inactivated in our system. Please allow up to three (3) business days to process your request.
For Help: Reply HELP to any message.
Message, Voice and Data rates may apply: By participating in the SMS/MMS Service, you approve any such charges from your mobile carrier. Check your carrier’s plan for details. You acknowledge and agree that you are solely responsible and liable for obtaining, maintaining, and paying all charges related to your mobile device(s).
No Guarantee: Roth Staffing is not responsible for incomplete, lost, late, or misdirected messages, including (but not limited to) undelivered messages resulting from any form of filtering by your mobile carrier or service provider or otherwise.
General Communications: You agree to receive notifications from Roth Staffing, its representatives, employees, and agents, through any means authorized under these terms, including text messages that use automatic telephone dialing technology.
Carriers: Supported carriers include all major United States carriers, including AT&T, Verizon Wireless, T-Mobile®, Sprint, and others.
Termination: Roth Staffing reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to cancel or suspend any or all of the SMS/MMS Service, in whole or in part, for any reason, with or without notice to you.
How You Can Access or Correct Your Information
If a user’s Personally Identifiable Information changes, such as phone number, e-mail address or address, or if a user no longer desires Roth Staffing services, contact IT Privacy Department by postal mail or e-mail (see below).
“Do Not Track” Signals
Some internet browsers incorporate a “Do Not Track” feature that signals to websites you visit that you do not want to have your online activity tracked. Given that there is not a uniform way that browsers communicate the “Do Not Track” signal, our Sites do not currently interpret, respond to or alter their practices when they receive “Do Not Track” signals.
Security
We maintain commercially reasonable security measures to protect the Personally Identifiable Information we collect and store from loss, misuse, destruction, or unauthorized access. However, no security measure or modality of data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. Although we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personally Identifiable Information, we cannot guarantee absolute security.
Children’s Privacy
Our Sites and Services are not intended for children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect, use, or disclose personal information from children under 13.
Notice to Nevada Residents
Nevada law allows Nevada residents to opt-out of the sale of certain types of personal information. Subject to a number of exceptions, Nevada law defines “sale” to mean the exchange of certain types of personal information for monetary consideration to a person for the person to license or sell the information to additional persons. We do not currently sell personal information as defined in the Nevada law. However, if you are a Nevada resident, you still may submit a verified request to opt-out of sales and we will record your instructions and incorporate them in the future if our policy changes. Opt-out requests may be sent to privacy@rothstaffing.com.
Notice to California Residents
The California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) requires that we provide California residents with a privacy policy that contains a comprehensive description of our online and offline practices regarding the collection, use, disclosure, and sale of personal information and of the rights of California residents regarding their personal information.
The CCPA defines “personal information” to mean information that identifies, relates to, describes, is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or household. Personal information does not include information that is publicly available, deidentified or aggregate information. For purposes of this “Notice to California Residents” section we will refer to this information as “Personal Information.”
The CCPA contains an important limitation that is applicable to Roth Staffing.
Some of the CCPA’s privacy rights described below do not apply to Personal Information that is collected in the course of a natural person acting as a job applicant to, an employee of, or contractor of a business to the extent that the Personal Information is collected and used by the business solely within that context. Because we are a staffing company, much of the Personal Information we collect is subject to that exemption.
Right to Know About Personal Information Collected, Disclosed, or Sold
Your Right
If you are a California resident, you have the right to request that we disclose what Personal Information we have collected about you in the 12-month period preceding your request. This right includes the right to request any or all of the following:
Specific pieces of Personal Information that we have collected about you;
Categories of Personal Information we have collected about you;
Categories of sources from which the Personal Information was collected;
Categories of Personal Information that we sold (if applicable) or disclosed for a business purpose about you;
Categories of third parties to whom the Personal Information was sold (if applicable) or disclosed for a business purpose; and
The business or commercial purpose for collecting or, if applicable, selling Personal Information.
Please note that we are not required to:
Retain any Personal Information about you that was collected for a single one-time transaction if, in the ordinary course of business, that information about you is not retained;
Reidentify or otherwise link any data that, in the ordinary course of business, is not maintained in a manner that would be considered Personal Information; or
Provide the Personal Information to you more than twice in a 12-month period.
The CCPA defines “sell” to mean selling, renting, releasing, disclosing, disseminating, making available, transferring, or otherwise communicating orally, in writing, or by electronic or other means, a California resident’s Personal Information to another business or a third party for monetary or other valuable consideration.
Your privacy is our priority, and we do not monetize your Personal Information by selling it to third parties.
After you visit our Sites and/or use our Services, you may receive advertisements about Roth Staffing’s services when you visit other websites (i.e., social media sites, search engines or other websites that are unrelated to Roth Staffing). This happens because we use third-party vendors to provide you with information about our services based upon your interactions with our website.
These third-party vendors may work with additional providers in their relationship network that help provide the advertising services the third-party vendors provide to us.
Note, we use these third parties only to show you ads about Roth Staffing’s Services (i.e., we do not use third parties to advertise any other company’s products or services to you).
Our third-party vendors and, if applicable, providers in their relationship network, may use the information they collect for purposes that are unrelated to showing you ads about our services.
When this information is used for a purpose other than showing ads about our services or other services we have requested, it may constitute a “sale” of Personal Information under the CCPA. For additional detailed information, please refer to the Disclosure or Sale of Personal Information section below.
How to Submit a Request to Know
If you have an account, you must log into your account and submit your request to know through your account. If you do not have an account, you may submit a request to know through our interactive webform available here or by calling us at 1-888-297-1911.
Our Process for Verifying a Request to Know
You may only make a verifiable consumer request to know twice within a 12-month period.  The verifiable consumer request must describe your request with sufficient detail that allows us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it.
If we determine that your request is subject to an exemption, we will notify you of our determination. If we determine that your request is not subject to an exemption, we will comply with your request upon verification of your identity and, to the extent applicable, the identity of the California resident on whose behalf you are making such request.
Our verification process may differ depending on whether you maintain a password-protected account with us.
If you maintain a password-protected account, we may verify your identity through existing authentication practices available through your account. Prior to disclosing the requested information, we will ask you to re-authenticate yourself with respect to that account.
If you do not maintain a password-protected account, or if you are an account-holder but we suspect fraudulent or malicious activity with your account, we will verify your identity as follows:
Request to Know Categories of Personal Information: We will verify your identity to a “reasonable degree of certainty” by verifying at least two data points that you previously provided to us and which we have determined to be reliable for the purpose of verifying identities.
Request to Know Specific Pieces of Personal Information: We will verify your identity to a “reasonably high degree of certainty” by verifying at least three pieces of Personal Information previously provided to us and which we have determined to be reliable the purpose of verifying identities. In addition, you will be required to submit a signed declaration under penalty of perjury stating that you are the individual whose Personal Information is being requested.
We will only use Personal Information provided in a verifiable consumer request to verify the requestor’s identity or authority to make the request. We cannot respond to your request or provide you with Personal Information if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the Personal Information relates to you.
Collection of Personal Information
The following tables present the categories of Personal Information that we have collected, the categories of sources from which that information was collected, and the categories of third parties with whom we shared that Personal Information for the 12 months preceding the Effective Date of this Privacy Policy. For ease of reference, we have divided the tables into the types of Personal Information we collect depending on how you interact with our Services.
If you browse jobs on our Sites, subscribe to one of our blogs, register for a webinar, contact us, download a publication or one of our mobile applications, use our chat feature, submit a Remarkable Experience or Roth Hero form, or contact us for support:
Categories of Personal Information Collected
Categories of Sources from which Personal Information was Collected
Business or Commercial Purpose for the Collection
Categories of Third Parties with whom We Share Personal Information
Identifiers (name, email address, postal address, telephone number, preferred name, suffix, honorifics)
Consumers, data aggregators, consumer data resellers
Providing customer service
Service providers, government entities, internet service providers, data analytics providers, data aggregators, operating systems and platforms, communication gateways, social media companies, internet cookie information recipients, advertisers, customers, prospective customers, subsidiaries
Professional or employment-related information (job title(s), professional or employment-related information, employment history)
Same
Same
Service providers, government entities, operating systems and platforms, communication gateways, social media companies, internet cookie information recipients, customers, prospective customers, subsidiaries
Audio/visual and olfactory information (voice recordings/audio information, video recordings, photographs, CCTV records, voicemails, and face/visual information)
Same
Same
Operating systems and platforms, social media companies, customers, prospective customers, subsidiaries
Internet or other electronic network activity information (browsing history, search history, and information regarding a consumer’s interaction with an Internet website, application, or advertisement)
Same
Same
Service providers, internet service providers, data analytics providers, operating systems and platforms, social media companies, internet cookie information recipients, subsidiaries
As discussed above, we also receive this type of Personal Information through third-parties to whom consumers have voluntarily provided their information with the expectation that staffing companies, such as Roth Staffing, will receive it.
If you create an account or apply for a job (which automatically creates an account):
Categories of Personal Information Collected
Categories of Sources from which Personal Information was Collected
Business or Commercial Purpose for the Collection
Categories of Third Parties with whom We Share Personal Information
Identifiers (name, email address, postal address, telephone number, preferred name, suffix, honorifics)
Consumers, data aggregators, consumer data resellers
Maintaining or servicing accounts
Service providers, government entities, internet service providers, data analytics providers, data aggregators, operating systems and platforms, communication gateways, social media companies, internet cookie information recipients, advertisers, customers, prospective customers, subsidiaries
Professional or employment-related information (job title(s), professional or employment-related information, employment history)
Same
Same
Service providers, government entities, operating systems and platforms, communication gateways, social media companies, internet cookie information recipients, customers, prospective customers, subsidiaries
Audio/visual and olfactory information (voice recordings/audio information, video recordings, photographs, CCTV records, voicemails, and face/visual information)
Same
Same
Operating systems and platforms, social media companies, customers, prospective customers, subsidiaries
Internet or other electronic network activity information (browsing history, search history, and information regarding a consumer’s interaction with an Internet website, application, or advertisement)
Same
Same
Service providers, internet service providers, data analytics providers, operating systems and platforms, social media companies, internet cookie information recipients, subsidiaries
If we hire you to work for one of our clients we may collect (in addition to the above categories):
Categories of Personal Information Collected
Categories of Sources from which Personal Information was Collected
Business or Commercial Purpose for the Collection
Categories of Third Parties with whom We Share Personal Information
Identifiers (name, email address, postal address, telephone number, preferred name, suffix, honorifics)
Employees
We collect this information for the operational purpose of providing employment to candidates
Service providers, government entities, internet service providers, data analytics providers, data aggregators, operating systems and platforms, communication gateways, social media companies, internet cookie information recipients, advertisers, customers, prospective customers, subsidiaries
Biometric identifiers (fingerprints, hair color, eye color, retina scans, facial recognition, voice, other biometric data)
Same
Same
N/A
Government-issued identifiers (social security number, driver’s license number, passport number, tribal ID number, other type of state or foreign identification number)
Same
Same
Service providers, government entities, operating systems and platforms, subsidiaries
Audio/visual and olfactory information (voice recordings/audio information, video recordings, photographs, CCTV records, voicemails, and face/visual information)
Same
Same
Operating systems and platforms, social media companies, customers, prospective customers, subsidiaries
Professional or employment-related information (job title(s), professional or employment-related information, employment history)
Same
Same
Service providers, government entities, operating systems and platforms, communication gateways, social media companies, internet cookie information recipients, customers, prospective customers, subsidiaries
Financial information (financial account numbers, insurance account numbers, payment card data, consumer reporting data, credit scores)
Same
Same
Service providers, operating systems and platforms
Education information (information that is not “publicly available personally identifiable information” as defined in the California Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (20 U.S.C. section 1232g, 34 C.F.R. Part 99)
Same
Same
Service providers, operating systems and platforms, customers, prospective customers, subsidiaries
Health information (information about payment for healthcare services, data collected by a healthcare provider or health insurance company subject to HIPAA or CMIA, disability status information, medical fitness for work records, inferred health data, patient records, information about a consumer’s diagnosis or treatment for health conditions, clinical trial records)
Same
Same
Service providers, government entities, operating systems and platforms
Government reporting and/or benefits information (race, color, sex/gender, age (40 and older), national origin, ancestry, citizenship status, marital status, military or veteran status)
Same
Same
Service providers, government entities, operating systems and platforms, customers only for their government-reporting obligations
Internet or other electronic network activity information (browsing history, search history, and information regarding a consumer’s interaction with an Internet website, application, or advertisement)
Same
Same
Service providers, internet service providers, data analytics providers, operating systems and platforms, social media companies, internet cookie information recipients, subsidiaries
Geolocation data
Same
Same
Service providers, internet service providers, data analytics providers, operating systems and platforms, social media companies, internet cookie information recipients, subsidiaries
Inferences (profile reflecting a consumer’s preferences:
Preferences
Characteristics
Psychological trends
Predispositions
Behavior
Attitudes
Intelligence
Abilities
Aptitudes
Service providers, operating systems and platforms, customers, prospective customers, subsidiaries
We collect the following from third parties:
Categories of Personal Information Collected
Categories of Sources from which Personal Information was Collected
Business or Commercial Purpose for the Collection
Categories of Third Parties with whom We Share Personal Information
Identifiers (name, email address, postal address, telephone number, preferred name, suffix, honorifics)
Data aggregators, consumer data resellers, social media companies, service providers, government entities
Providing customer service and for the operational purpose of providing employment to candidates
Service providers, government entities, internet service providers, data analytics providers, data aggregators, operating systems and platforms, communication gateways, social media companies, internet cookie information recipients, advertisers, customers
Government-issued identifiers (social security number, driver’s license number, passport number, tribal ID number, other type of state or foreign identification number)
Government entities
Same
Service providers, government entities, operating systems and platforms, customers only for their government-reporting obligations
Audio/visual and olfactory information (voice recordings/audio information, video recordings, photographs, CCTV records, voicemails, and face/visual information)
Social media companies
Same
Operating systems and platforms, social media companies, customers, prospective customers, subsidiaries
Professional or employment-related information (job title(s), professional or employment-related information, employment history)
Data aggregators, consumer data resellers, social media companies, service providers, prospective customers, customers, subsidiaries
Same
Service providers, government entities, operating systems and platforms, communication gateways, social media companies, internet cookie information recipients, customers, prospective customers, subsidiaries
Financial information (financial account numbers, insurance account numbers, payment card data, consumer reporting data, credit scores)
Service providers
Service providers, operating systems and platforms
Health information (information about payment for healthcare services, data collected by a healthcare provider or health insurance company subject to HIPAA or CMIA, disability status information, medical fitness for work records, inferred health data, patient records, information about a consumer’s diagnosis or treatment for health conditions, clinical trial records)
Service providers
Service providers, government entities,  operating systems and platforms
Internet or other electronic network activity information (browsing history, search history, and information regarding a consumer’s interaction with an Internet website, application, or advertisement)
Service providers, operating systems and platforms, data aggregators, social media companies, communication gateways
Service providers, internet service providers, data analytics providers, operating systems and platforms, social media companies, internet cookie information recipients, subsidiaries
Geolocation data
Service providers, operating systems and platforms, social media companies, communication gateways
Service providers, internet service providers, data analytics providers, operating systems and platforms, social media companies, internet cookie information recipients, subsidiaries
Inferences (profile reflecting a consumer’s preferences:
Preferences
Characteristics
Psychological trends
Predispositions
Behavior
Attitudes
Intelligence
Abilities
Aptitudes
Service providers, data aggregators, operating systems and platforms, social media companies, prospective customers, customers, subsidiaries
Service providers, operating systems and platforms, customers, prospective customers, subsidiaries
As discussed, many of these categories of Personal Information are exempt from the CCPA because they are collected in the course of a natural person acting as a job applicant to, an employee of, or contractor of Roth Staffing.
Disclosure or Sale of Personal Information
Your privacy is our priority, and we do not monetize your Personal Information by selling it to third parties.
After you visit our Sites and/or use our Services, you may receive advertisements about Roth Staffing’s services when you visit other websites (i.e., social media sites, search engines or other websites that are unrelated to Roth Staffing). This happens because we use third-party vendors to provide you with information about our services based upon your interactions with our website.
These third-party vendors may work with additional providers in their relationship network that help provide the advertising services the third-party vendors provide to us.
Note, we use these third parties only to show you ads about Roth Staffing’s Services (i.e., we do not use third parties to advertise any other company’s products or services to you).
Our third-party vendors and, if applicable, providers in their relationship network, may use the information they collect for purposes that are unrelated to showing you ads about our services.
When this information is used for a purpose other than showing ads about our services or other services we have requested, it may constitute a “sale” of personal information under the CCPA.
Pursuant to the CCPA, in the preceding twelve (12) months, we have sold the following categories of Personal Information for the purpose of showing you ads about Roth Staffing’s Services:
Identifiers
Internet or other similar network activity
Geolocation data
In this limited context, we may sell your Personal Information to the following categories of third parties:
Third-party advertising partners or advertising networks
The CCPA prohibits third parties who purchase the personal information we hold from reselling it unless you have received explicit notice and an opportunity to opt-out of further sales.
We do not sell the Personal Information of minors under 16 years of age without affirmative authorization.
The following is a list of categories of Personal Information that we may have disclosed for a business or commercial purpose in the 12 months preceding the Effective Date of this Privacy Policy:
Identifiers (name, email address, postal address, telephone number, preferred name, suffix, honorifics)
Government-issued identifiers (social security number, driver’s license number, passport number, tribal ID number, other type of state or foreign identification number)
Government reporting and/or benefits information (race, color, sex/gender, age (40 and older), national origin, ancestry, citizenship status, marital status, military or veteran status)
Biometric identifiers (fingerprints, hair color, eye color, retina scans, facial recognition, voice, other biometric data)
Audio/visual and olfactory information (voice recordings/audio information, video recordings, photographs, CCTV records, voicemails, face/visual information)
Professional or employment-related information (job title(s), professional or employment-related information, employment history)
Education information (information that is not “publicly available personally identifiable information” as defined in the California Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (20 U.S.C. section 1232g, 34 C.F.R. Part 99)
Health information (information about payment for healthcare services, data collected by a healthcare provider or health insurance company subject to HIPAA or CMIA, disability status information, medical fitness for work records, inferred health data, patient records, information about a consumer’s diagnosis or treatment for health conditions, clinical trial records)
Financial information (financial account numbers, insurance account numbers, payment card data, consumer reporting data, credit scores)
Internet or other electronic network activity information (browsing history, search history, and information regarding a consumer’s interaction with an Internet website, application, or advertisement)
Geolocation data
Inferences (profile reflecting a consumer’s preferences):
Preferences
Characteristics
Psychological trends
Predispositions
Behavior
Attitudes
Intelligence
Abilities
Aptitudes
Right to Request Deletion of Personal Information
Your Right
If you are a California resident, you have the right to request that we delete the Personal Information about you that we have collected and retained, subject to certain exceptions. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request, we will delete (and direct our service providers to delete) your Personal Information from our records unless an exception applies. Many of the categories of Personal Information we collect are exempt from the CCPA, including the right to of a consumer to request the deletion of the Personal Information, because they are collected in the course of a natural person acting as a job applicant to, an employee of, or contractor of Roth Staffing or emergency contact of such natural person acting as a job applicant to, an employee of, or contractor of Roth Staffing.
A business is not required to comply with a request to delete if it is necessary for the business to maintain the Personal Information in order to, for example, complete a transaction; detect security incidents; protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, or prosecute those responsible for that activity; exercise free speech, ensure the right of another consumer to exercise his or her right to free speech, or exercise another right provided for by law; comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act; comply with a legal obligation, or otherwise use the Personal Information, internally, in a lawful manner that is compatible with the context in which the consumer provided the information.
How to Submit a Request to Delete
If you have an account, you must log into your account and submit your request to delete through your account. If you do not have an account, you may submit a request to delete through our interactive webform available here or by calling us at 1-888-297-1911.
If you submit a request to delete online, you will be asked to confirm separately that you want your Personal Information deleted.
Our Process for Verifying a Request
If we determine that your request is subject to an exemption, we will notify you of our determination. If we determine that your request is not subject to an exemption, we will comply with your request upon verification of your identity and, to the extent applicable, the identity of the California resident on whose behalf you are making such request. Our verification process may differ depending on whether you maintain a password-protected account with us.
If you maintain a password-protected account, we may verify your identity through existing authentication practices available through your account. Prior to deleting the Personal Information, we will ask you to re-authenticate yourself with respect to that account.
If you do not maintain a password-protected account, or if you are an account-holder but we suspect fraudulent or malicious activity with your account, we will verify your identity either to a “reasonable degree of certainty” or a “reasonably high degree of certainty” depending on the sensitivity of the Personal Information and the risk of harm to you by unauthorized deletion.
We will verify your identity to a “reasonable degree of certainty” by verifying at least two data points that you previously provided to us and which we have determined to be reliable for the purpose of verifying identities.
We will verify your identity to a “reasonably high degree of certainty” by verifying at least three pieces of Personal Information previously provided to us and which we have determined to be reliable the purpose of verifying identities.  In addition, you will be required to submit a signed declaration under penalty of perjury stating that you are the individual whose Personal Information is being requested.
Notice of Right to Opt-Out of Sale of Personal Information
Your Right
If you are a California resident, you have the right to direct a business that sells (or may in the future sell) your Personal Information to stop selling your Personal Information and to refrain from doing so in the future.
The CCPA defines “sell” to mean selling, renting, releasing, disclosing, disseminating, making available, transferring, or otherwise communicating orally, in writing, or by electronic or other means, a California resident’s Personal Information to another business or a third party for monetary or other valuable consideration.
Your privacy is our priority, and we do not monetize your Personal Information by selling it to third parties.
After you visit our Sites and/or use our Services, you may receive advertisements about Roth Staffing’s services when you visit other websites (i.e., social media sites, search engines or other websites that are unrelated to Roth Staffing). This happens because we use third-party vendors to provide you with information about our services based upon your interactions with our website.
These third-party vendors may work with additional providers in their relationship network that help provide the advertising services the third-party vendors provide to us.
Note, we use these third parties only to show you ads about Roth Staffing’s Services (i.e., we do not use third parties to advertise any other company’s products or services to you).
Our third-party vendors and, if applicable, providers in their relationship network, may use the information they collect for purposes that are unrelated to showing you ads about our services.
When this information is used for a purpose other than showing ads about our services or other services we have requested, it may constitute a “sale” of Personal Information under the CCPA.
Pursuant to the CCPA, in the preceding twelve (12) months, we have sold the following categories of Personal Information for the purpose of showing you ads about Roth Staffing’s Services:
Identifiers
Internet or other similar network activity
Geolocation data
In this limited context, we may sell your Personal Information to the following categories of third parties:
Third-party advertising partners or advertising networks
The CCPA prohibits third parties who purchase the Personal Information we hold from reselling it unless you have received explicit notice and an opportunity to opt-out of further sales.
How to Opt Out from the Sale of Personal Information
To submit an opt-out request, you (or your authorized representative) may click one of the links below:
To opt-out from ultimatestaffing.com click here
To opt-out from ledgent.com click here
To opt-out from ledgenttech.com click here
To opt-out from adamsmartingroup.com click here
To opt-out from abouttalent.com click here
To opt-out from rothstaffing.com click here
Right to Non-Discrimination for the Exercise of a California Resident’s Privacy Rights
We will not discriminate against California residents if they exercise any of the rights provided in the CCPA as described in this section “Notice to California Residents.” As such, we will not deny goods or services to that California resident; charge different prices or rates for goods or services, including through the use of discounts or other benefits or imposing penalties; provide a different level or quality of goods or services to the California resident; or suggest that the California resident will receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services. However, we are permitted to charge a California resident a different price or rate, or provide a different level or quality of goods or services, if that difference is reasonably related to the value provided to us by the individual’s data.
Authorized Agents
California residents may use an authorized agent to submit a request to know or delete on your behalf.
If you use an authorized agent to submit a request to know or request to delete, we may require that (1) the authorized agent provide proof of your written permission and (2) you verify your identity directly with us. These requirements do not apply if you have provided the authorized agent with a power of attorney pursuant to California Probate Code sections 4000 to 4465.
Shine the Light Law
We do not disclose personal information obtained through our Sites or Services to third-parties for their direct marketing purposes. Accordingly, we have no obligations under California Civil Code § 1798.83.
How to Contact the Company
Roth Staffing welcomes and encourages your comments regarding its Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about the policy or your experience with our Sites, you may contact us by postal mail or e-mail, as follows:
Attn: IT Privacy Department
Roth Staffing Companies, L.P.
450 N. State College Blvd.
Orange, CA 92868
E-mail Address: privacy@rothstaffing.com
Terms of Service
Last Updated: December 30, 2019
Welcome to the Roth Staffing Companies, L.P., website, emails, and/or mobile applications together with any materials and services available therein (the “Sites”). Throughout these terms, "Roth Staffing," "we," "us" and "our" refer to Roth Staffing Companies, L.P., and its divisions, subsidiaries, and affiliates along with their directors, officers, employees, agents, and representatives. Your use of and access to the Sites is subject to the following terms and conditions ("Terms of Service"), which you affirmatively accept by using the Sites. Please read these Terms of Service carefully and ensure that you understand them before you use the Sites.
We reserve the right to modify the contents of the Sites at any time, including the features, availability, or operation of the Sites, these Terms of Service, and/or any policy or notice posted on the Sites. You agree to monitor the Sites for any changes and that the continued use of the Sites following the posting of any changes signals your understanding of, and agreement to, such changes.
EACH TIME YOU USE THE SITES, THIS AGREEMENT AS IT THEN READS WILL GOVERN YOUR USE. ACCORDINGLY, WHEN YOU USE THE SITES, YOU SHOULD CHECK THE DATE OF THESE TERMS WHICH APPEAR AT THE TOP OF THIS AGREEMENT AND REVIEW ANY CHANGES SINCE THE LAST VERSION.
Eligibility and Ability to Accept Terms of Service
The word "you" as used in the Terms of Service will apply to users who browse, access or use the Sites on their own behalf and/or on behalf of an entity. If you use the Sites on behalf of an employer, organization, agency, institution, or other entity, then (a) "you" includes you and that entity, and (b) you represent and warrant that you are an authorized representative of the entity with the authority to bind the entity to the Terms of Service, and that you agree to these Terms of Service on the entity's behalf
Each time you use the Sites, you signify your agreement, and the agreement of all persons you represent, without limitation or qualification, to be bound by these Terms of Service, and you represent and warrant that you have the legal authority to agree to and accept these Terms of Service on behalf of yourself and all persons or entities you represent. If you do not agree with each provision of these Terms of Service, or you are not authorized to agree to and accept these Terms of Service, you may not use the Sites. You also affirm that you are over the age of legal majority, can form legally binding agreements under applicable law, and are fully able and competent to enter into the terms, conditions, obligations, affirmations, representations, and warranties set forth in these Terms of Service, and to qualify under, abide by, and comply with these Terms of Service.
Accuracy, Completeness and Timeliness of Information
The Sites provide a passive forum for users to obtain employment and career information. Roth Staffing makes no representations or warranties regarding the effectiveness of the Sites or their content in meeting employment or career objectives. By submitting or entering your information to the Sites ("Submitted Information"), you agree that you grant Roth Staffing a perpetual, non-exclusive, irrevocable, royalty free, fully paid-up, transferable, fully sublicensable, worldwide license and right, but not the obligation, to use, copy, modify, display, distribute, download, store, reproduce, transmit, publish, transfer, adapt, create derivative works in any manner, in entirety or a portion of, of your Submitted Information, and by any means, forever and worldwide. You represent and warrant that you have all rights necessary to grant the licenses granted in this section, and that your Submitted Information, and your provision thereof through and in connection with the Sites, are complete and accurate, and are not fraudulent, tortious or otherwise in violation of any applicable law or any right of any third party. You further irrevocably waive any “moral rights” or other rights with respect to attribution of authorship or integrity of materials regarding each Submission that you may have under any applicable law under any legal theory.
Roth Staffing may (but has no obligation to) screen, evaluate, or monitor any Submitted Information. Roth Staffing, therefore, makes no representation regarding the reliability, accuracy, completeness, validity, or truthfulness of any Submitted Information. Roth Staffing reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to delete, remove, refuse to display, or block any Submitted Information, discontinue services, remove or alter content, or retract positions at any time without incurring any obligations. You acknowledge and agree that Roth Staffing may retain copies of your Submitted Information and disclose your Submitted Information to a third party if Roth Staffing believes that it is necessary to: (i) protect the integrity of the Sites; (ii) protect rights of Roth Staffing; (iii) comply with any court order; (iv) comply with any legal proceedings; (v) assert Roth Staffing’s claim under this Terms of Service; and (vi) satisfy any claims regarding violations of third party's rights. We may disclose information regarding your access to and use of the Sites, and the circumstances surrounding such access and use, to anyone for any reason or purpose.
For clarity, certain information that you provide to Roth Staffing through the Sites may also be governed by Roth Staffing’s Privacy Policy. You represent and warrant that any information you provide in connection with the Sites is and will remain accurate and complete, and that you will maintain and update such information as needed.
The Sites should not be relied upon or used as the sole basis for making significant decisions without consulting primary or more accurate, complete or timely sources of information.
Use of the Sites
Subject to and conditioned on your compliance with the Terms of Service, Roth Staffing grants you a limited, non-exclusive, non-transferable, non-assignable, revocable license to view and temporarily download a copy of the materials displayed on the Sites solely for your personal and non-commercial use for yourself or within your organization. All materials displayed or made available on the Sites, including, but not limited to, graphics, documents, text, images, sound, video, audio, artwork, software, and HTML code (collectively, the "Material") are the exclusive property of Roth Staffing or its content suppliers. The Material is protected by U.S. and international copyright laws and any other applicable intellectual property rules, regulations, and laws. Except as expressly permitted herein, you shall not (i) use, copy, modify, display, delete, distribute, download, store, reproduce, transmit, publish, sell, re-sell, adapt, reverse engineer, or create derivative works of the Material, or (ii) use the Material on other web sites or any media, e.g., networking environment, without Roth Staffing’s prior written consent. All trademarks, service marks, and logos (the "Marks") displayed on the Sites are the exclusive property of Roth Staffing and their respective owners. You shall not use the Marks in any manner without Roth Staffing’s and their respective owners' prior written consent. Roth Staffing neither warrants nor represents that use of information and/or material from the Sites will not infringe rights of third parties not affiliated with Roth Staffing.
Improper use of information provided on the Sites and improper use of any hardware or software, including the intent to damage or interfere with the proper working of the Sites or to surreptitiously intercept any system, data or personal information from the Sites, is strictly prohibited. You may not interrupt or attempt to interrupt the operation of the Sites in any way and Roth Staffing reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to terminate access to or use of the Sites at any time without notice. Termination of access or use of the Sites will not waive or affect any right or relief to which Roth Staffing may be entitled at law or in equity.
In connection with your use, you agree NOT to: (1) violate any local, state, and federal rules, regulations and statutes, including, but not limited to, U.S. export laws and regulations, anti-discrimination, or equal opportunity employment laws; (2) infringe any intellectual property and privacy rights, including, but not limited to, patent, copyright, trademark, or trade secrets, of any third party; (3) breach or attempt to breach any security measures of the Sites; (4) use any device, process, or mechanism to monitor, retrieve, search, or access, e.g., spider or robot, the Sites or any Material without Roth Staffing’s prior written consent; (5) access or attempt to access any account or login of any third party listed on the Sites; (6) copy, modify, reproduce, delete, distribute, download, store, transmit, sell, re-sell, rent, lease, publish, reverse engineer, translate, or create derivative works of any Material, except for materials that have been submitted and are owned by you; (7) post or submit any inaccurate, false, or incomplete information, such as your resume, biographical data, or employment information; (8) impersonate any person or entity; (9) forge any header information in any electronic posting or mail; (10) harvest or collect information about users of the Sites; (11) frame or mirror any portion of the Sites, or otherwise incorporate any portion of the Sites into any product or service; (12) remove any copyright, trademark or other proprietary rights notice from the Sites; (13) use the Sites for any commercial purpose, or for any purpose that is otherwise fraudulent or otherwise harmful; (14) interfere with or disrupt the operation of the Sites or the servers or networks used to make the Sites available, including by hacking or defacing any portion of the Sites; or (15) misrepresent yourself, your affiliation with any third party, or your entity.
You also agree NOT to upload, post, transmit, or store any material that: (1) is unlawful, offensive, defamatory, fraudulent, deceptive, misleading, harmful, threatening, harassing, obscene, or objectionable; (2) breaches any of your contractual or confidentiality obligations; (3) disrupts or interferes with the normal operations of the Sites, such as posting or transmitting viruses, continuous posting of repetitive materials, or posting abnormally large load; or (4) is not permitted by Roth Staffing, including, but not limited to, any unauthorized advertising materials, unsolicited promotional materials, "junk mail," "spam mail," "chain letters," pyramid schemes, franchises, distributorship, club membership, sales arrangement, or otherwise unacceptable materials.
You may use personal information available on the Sites only if you are an authorized user and only for the purposes for which it was provided, including job placement and similar, employment-related purposes. If you refer a friend or colleague to our Sites by providing us with their contact information, you represent that you have their permission to do so. If you do not have their consent to share their contact information, then please do not refer your friend or colleague to the Sites. Any use of personal information obtained from the Sites by any user must be consistent with these purposes, with the Privacy Policy posted on the Sites, and with any other privacy promises made by Roth Staffing on the Sites. Users warrant and represent that personal information supplied to or obtained from the Sites was collected, disclosed to Roth Staffing and otherwise processed only in strict compliance with applicable law, including privacy and data protection requirements and restrictions. Users warrant and represent that any personal information they access, manage or maintain on behalf of Roth Staffing is subject to reasonable and appropriate security measures that comply with all applicable laws and include, at minimum, administrative, physical and technical safeguards that protect against the loss, misuse, or unauthorized access, acquisition, alteration or destruction of information.
Account and Password
The Sites may present you with opportunities to open a(n) account(s) with the Sites. We may reject, or require that you change, any username, password, or other information that you provide to us in registering or opening a(n) account(s). It is your sole responsibility to (a) maintain the confidentiality of your account logon and password; (b) frequently update and revise your password; and (c) promptly notify Roth Staffing if there is any unauthorized use of your account or any breach of security. You are solely responsible for the security of and any use or misuse of your username and password.
Links
The Sites may contain links to other websites maintained by third parties and not owned or operated by Roth Staffing (“Other Sites”). Links to the Other Sites are provided merely for your convenience.
Roth Staffing has not necessarily reviewed all of the information on the Other Sites and is not responsible for the content of the Other Sites or any information, material, products or services that may be offered through any of these Other Sites. Roth Staffing is not responsible for any losses, damages, or other liabilities incurred as the result of the use of any of the Other Sites.
You are solely responsible for your access of the Other Sites.
Our Proprietary Rights
With the exception of content owned by, or licensed from, third parties, the Sites and all materials therein or transferred thereby, including, without limitation, software, images, text, graphics, illustrations, logos, patents, trademarks, service marks, copyrights, photographs, audio, videos, music, and content (the, "Roth Staffing Content"), and all intellectual property rights related thereto, are the exclusive property of Roth Staffing. Except as explicitly provided herein, nothing in the Terms of Service shall be deemed to create a license in or under, any such Intellectual property rights, and you agree not to sell, license, rent, modify, distribute, copy, reproduce, transmit, publicly display, publicly perform, publish, adapt, edit or create derivative works from any materials or content accessible on the Sites. Use of the Roth Staffing Content or materials on the Sites for any purpose not expressly permitted by the Terms of Service is strictly prohibited.
If you participate in any evaluation regarding the Sites or otherwise provide Roth Staffing suggestions, comments, ideas, opinions, recommendations for the modification, correction, improvement, or enhancement of the Sites, or other feedback regarding the Sites (collectively, "Feedback"), you agree that Roth Staffing shall own such Feedback. Accordingly, you understand and accept that Roth Staffing will be free to use, disclose, reproduce, license or otherwise distribute, commercialize and exploit the Feedback as it sees fit, entirely without obligation or restriction of any kind and without compensation to you. You agree not to provide any Feedback that is false or misleading or that breaches any agreement you have with a third party.
Notice of Copyright Infringement
The Digital Millennium Copyright Act of 1998 (the “DMCA”) provides recourse for copyright owners who believe that material appearing on the internet infringes their rights under U.S. copyright law. If you believe in good faith that materials available on the Sites infringe your copyright, you (or your agent) may send a written notice by mail or e-mail, requesting that Roth Staffing remove such material or block access to it. If you believe in good faith that someone has wrongly filed a notice of copyright infringement against you, the DMCA permits you to send to Roth Staffing a counter-notice. Notices and counter-notices must meet the then-current statutory requirements imposed by the DMCA. See http://www.copyright.gov/ for details. Notices and counter-notices must be sent in writing to:
Roth Staffing Companies, L.P.450 North State College BoulevardOrange, CA 92868Attn: DMCA Agent
Email: dmcaagent@rothstaffing.com
UNDER FEDERAL LAW, IF YOU KNOWINGLY MISREPRESENT THAT ONLINE MATERIAL IS INFRINGING, YOU MAY BE SUBJECT TO CRIMINAL PROSECUTION FOR PERJURY AND CIVIL PENALTIES, INCLUDING MONETARY DAMAGES, COURT COSTS, AND ATTORNEYS' FEES.
DISCLAIMERS
You understand and agree that Roth Staffing (a) does not warrant that you will receive any employment or job offers through the Sites; (b) shall not be responsible for any employment offers, employment screenings, employment decisions, and actual employment presented by third parties; (c) does not guarantee the accuracy, completeness, validity, or timeliness of information listed by any third parties; (d) shall not be responsible for any materials posted by third parties, including, but not limited to, job openings and employment listings; and (e) is neither your employer nor your agent in any regard. You shall use your own judgment and caution in evaluating any prospective employers and any information provided by any third party.
USE OF THE SITES IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK. THE SITES ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS. WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO RESTRICT OR TERMINATE ACCESS TO THE SITE OR ANY FEATURE OR PART THEREOF AT ANY TIME. ROTH STAFFING EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO: IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND ANY WARRANTIES THAT MATERIALS ON THE SITES ARE NONINFRINGING, AS WELL AS WARRANTIES IMPLIED FROM A COURSE OF PERFORMANCE, USAGE OR TRADE, OR COURSE OF DEALING; THAT ACCESS TO THE SITES WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE; THAT THE SITES WILL BE SECURE; THAT THE SITES OR THE SERVER THAT MAKES THE SITES AVAILABLE WILL BE VIRUS-FREE; OR THAT INFORMATION ON THE SITES WILL BE COMPLETE, ACCURATE, TIMELY, OR AUTHENTIC. IF ANY CONTENT IS DOWNLOADED FROM OR UPLOADED TO THE SITE, IT IS DONE AT USER'S SOLE RISK AND DISCRETION. EACH USER IS SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO HIS/HER COMPUTER SYSTEM OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE DOWNLOAD OR UPLOAD OF ANY SUCH MATERIALS. NO ADVICE OR INFORMATION, WHETHER ORAL OR WRITTEN, OBTAINED FROM ROTH STAFFING OR THROUGH OR FROM THE SITES SHALL CREATE ANY WARRANTY OF ANY KIND. ROTH STAFFING DOES NOT MAKE ANY WARRANTIES OR REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING THE USE OF THE CONTENT ON THE SITES IN TERMS OF THEIR COMPLETENESS, CORRECTNESS, ACCURACY, ADEQUACY, USEFULNESS, TIMELINESS, RELIABILITY, AUTHENTICITY, OR OTHERWISE.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
YOU AGREE TO ASSUME ALL RISKS ASSOCIATED WITH, ARISING OUT OF, OR RESULTING FROM YOUR USE OF THE SITES OR ANY SUBMITTED MATERIALS, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE RISKS OF FINANCIAL LOSS, PHYSICAL HARM, PROPERTY DAMAGE, DEALING WITH OTHER USERS OF THE SITES, STRANGERS, MINORS, OR FOREIGN NATIONALS, AND PERSONS ACTING UNDER FALSE PRETENSE. YOU FURTHER AGREE TO RELEASE ROTH STAFFING, ITS DIVISIONS, PARENTS, SUBSIDIARIES, AFFILIATES, OFFICERS, AGENTS, AND EMPLOYEES, FROM ALL CLAIMS, DEMANDS, DAMAGES (DIRECT, INDIRECT, AND CONSEQUENTIAL) OF ANY KIND OR NATURE, KNOWN OR UNKNOWN, ASSOCIATED WITH, ARISING OUT OF, OR RESULTING FROM YOUR USAGE OF THE SITES, YOUR SUBMITTED MATERIALS, OR ANY TRANSACTIONS RELATED TO OR RESULTING FROM YOUR USE OF THE SITES. YOU FURTHER UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT IN NO EVENT SHALL ROTH STAFFING, ITS DIVISIONS, PARENTS, SUBSIDIARIES, AFFILIATES, OFFICERS, AGENTS, EMPLOYEES, AND SUPPLIERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL DAMAGES, OR DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, GOODWILL, REVENUE, DATA, OR USE, INCURRED BY YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION IN CONTRACT, TORT, NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY, BREACH OF STATUTORY DUTY, BREACH OR FAILURE OF WARRANTY, OR ANY OTHER BASIS, EVEN IF ROTH STAFFING HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. IN THE EVENT SOME JURISDICTIONS PROHIBIT THE EXCLUSION OF CERTAIN WARRANTIES, THE LIMITATION OF LIABILITY, OR THE DISCLAIMER OF CERTAIN DAMAGES, ROTH STAFFING’S AGGREGATE LIABILITY FOR ANY DAMAGES SHALL NOT EXCEED U.S. $15.
Indemnification
To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, you agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless Roth Staffing and its divisions, parents, subsidiaries, affiliates, and their officers, directors, employees, contractors, agents, licensors, service providers, subcontractors and suppliers, from and against any and all losses, liabilities, expenses, damages, claims, and costs, including reasonable attorneys' fees and court costs, arising or resulting from: (i) your use of the Sites, including any data or content transmitted or received by you; (ii) your violation of any of the terms in these Terms of Service or any other agreement you have with Roth Staffing, including without limitation your breach of any of the representations and warranties herein; (iii) your violation of any applicable law, rule or regulation, including without limitation any applicable data protection laws; (iv) any claims or damages that arise as a result of your Submitted Information; (v) any other party’s access or use of the Sites with your account or log-in information; and/or (vi) your intentional or willful misconduct or negligence. If technical disruption of the Sites
or the systems supporting the Sites occurs due to your action or inaction, you agree to be responsible for any and all losses, liabilities, expenses, damages and costs, including reasonable attorneys' fees and court costs, arising or resulting from that disruption. Roth Staffing reserves the right, at its own expense, to assume exclusive defense and control of any matter otherwise subject to indemnification and, in such case, you agree to cooperate with Roth Staffing in defense of such matter.
General
The Terms of Service is governed by the laws of the State of California, United States of America, without giving effect to any principles of conflict of laws. Any controversy or claim arising out of or relating to this Agreement, or the breach thereof, shall be settled by arbitration administered by either JAMS or the American Arbitration Association under its Commercial Arbitration Rules, and judgment on the award rendered by the arbitrator may be entered in any court having jurisdiction thereof. The arbitration will be before a single arbitrator. The place of arbitration will be Orange, California, United States of America. Notwithstanding the foregoing, you or Roth Staffing may seek injunctive relief from an appropriate court located in Orange, California prior to or during the arbitration. The Sites are controlled or operated (or both) from the United States, and are not intended to subject Roth Staffing to any non-U.S. jurisdiction or law. Roth Staffing makes no representations that the Sites are appropriate or available for use in locations outside of the United States or the European Union. Those who choose to access the Sites from other locations do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with all United States laws as well as local laws, if and to the extent local laws are applicable. These Terms of Service along with any posted policies or operating rules constitute the entire understanding of Roth Staffing and you and supersedes any prior or contemporaneous communications and proposals, whether oral or written, between the parties with respect to the Site. If any provision of these Terms of Service is unlawful, void or unenforceable, the remaining provisions shall remain in full force.
How to Contact Us
Questions or comments about these Terms of Service or the Sites may be directed to:
Roth Staffing Companies, L.P.450 North State College BoulevardOrange, CA
92868Attn:
IT Privacy Department
Thank you for visiting our site.
Profile Agreement
I certify that all of the information contained in my profile, resume, any other documents filled out in connection with my application for employment or with the Company’s representation of me for direct hire opportunities, and any information provided in any interview, is true, complete and correct, and I understand that any misrepresentation, omission or falsification of any information provided by me may result in disqualification from further representation by the Company, consideration for employment with the Company or the Company’s clients, or, if hired by a Company client or by the Company, dismissal from employment. I authorize the Company to contact my former employers, references, and any and all other persons and organizations for information bearing upon my qualifications for employment. I further authorize the listed employers, schools and personal references to give the Company any and all information about my previous employment and education, along with any other pertinent information they may have.
Our Headquarters
450 N. State College Blvd.
Orange, CA 92868
714.939.8600
Quicklinks
Search For Jobs
Our Services
Our Company
Our People
Work With Us
Testimonials
"I want to commend you for the terrific and immediate work that you have provided to us. Much of your success with helping us is due in large part to your constant, professional, and persistent invitation to stay connected and your periodic follow-ups to see how you can help us!"
- Client (Houston, TX)
"Your Sr. RPO Recruiter is a hard-working recruiter who takes the time to understand the company and its needs and identifies high caliber candidates for our company. He is always very responsive, dependable and professional. It is a pleasure partnering with him and we appreciate all of his hard work."
- Client (San Diego, CA)
"[Our Executive Recruiter] epitomizes professionalism and leadership in her profession. I’ve had the fortunate experience of working with her over the last two years and cannot overstate how much I appreciated her demeanor, her willingness to be an engaged business partner and her ability to find us great talent. She is clearly an expert in recruiting and talent management. She’s been instrumental in helping [our company] build its team. I strongly recommend her and look forward to more collaborations in the years to come."
- Client (Sacramento, CA)
"Thank you for all of the excellent support you guys have given us in 2016! This was a very challenging year for us and all of your support and efforts to keep us staffed was a tremendous help. 2017 will bring new challenges, but I’m comforted knowing your teams will be there to help us when we need it."
- Client (St. Louis, MO)
&uparrowTOP
©Copyright 1994-2020
Roth Staffing Companies, L.P. All Rights Reserved.
